<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
<string-array name="oneliner_array">
    <item>Life is wonderful. Without it we\'d all be dead.</item>
    <item>Daddy, why doesn\'t this magnet pick up this floppy disk?</item>
    <item>Give me ambiguity or give me something else.</item>
    <item>I.R.S.: We\'ve got what it takes to take what you\'ve got!</item>
    <item>We are born naked, wet and hungry. Then things get worse.</item>
    <item>Make it idiot proof and someone will make a better idiot.</item>
    <item>He who laughs last thinks slowest!</item>
    <item>Always remember you\'re unique, just like everyone else.</item>
    <item>"More hay, Trigger?" "No thanks, Roy, I'm stuffed!"</item>
    <item>A flashlight is a case for holding dead batteries.</item>
    <item>Lottery: A tax on people who are bad at math.</item>
    <item>Error, no keyboard - press F1 to continue.</item>
    <item>There\'s too much blood in my caffeine system.</item>
    <item>Artificial Intelligence usually beats real stupidity.</item>
    <item>Hard work has a future payoff. Laziness pays off now.</item>
    <item>"Very funny, Scotty. Now beam down my clothes."</item>
    <item>Puritanism: The haunting fear that someone, somewhere may be happy.</item>
    <item>Consciousness: that annoying time between naps.</item>
    <item>Don\'t take life too seriously, you won\'t get out alive.</item>
    <item>I don\'t suffer from insanity. I enjoy every minute of it.</item>
    <item>Better to understand a little than to misunderstand a lot.</item>
    <item>The gene pool could use a little chlorine.</item>
    <item>When there\'s a will, I want to be in it.</item>
    <item>Okay, who put a "stop payment" on my reality check?</item>
    <item>We have enough youth, how about a fountain of SMART?</item>
    <item>Programming is an art form that fights back.</item>
    <item>"Daddy, what does FORMATTING DRIVE C mean?"</item>
    <item>All wiyht. Rho sritched mg kegtops awound?</item>
    <item>My mail reader can beat up your mail reader.</item>
    <item>Never forget: 2 + 2 = 5 for extremely large values of 2.</item>
    <item>Nobody has ever, ever, EVER learned all of WordPerfect</item>.
    <item>To define recursion, we must first define recursion.</item>
    <item>Good programming is 99 percent sweat and 1 percent coffee.</item>
    <item>Home is where you hang your @</item>
    <item>The E-mail of the species is more deadly than the mail.</item>
    <item>A journey of a thousand sites begins with a single click.</item>
    <item>You can\'t teach a new mouse old clicks.</item>
    <item>Great groups from little icons grow.</item>
    <item>Speak softly and carry a cellular phone.</item>
    <item>C:\ is the root of all directories.</item>
    <item>Don\'t put all your hypes in one home page.</item>
    <item>Pentium wise; pen and paper foolish.</item>
    <item>The modem is the message.</item>
    <item>Too many clicks spoil the browse.</item>
    <item>The geek shall inherit the earth.</item>
    <item>A chat has nine lives.</item>
    <item>Don\'t byte off more than you can view.</item>
    <item>Fax is stranger than fiction.</item>
    <item>What boots up must come down.</item>
    <item>Windows will never cease.   (ed. oh sure...)</item>
    <item>In Gates we trust.    (ed.  yeah right....)</item>
    <item>Virtual reality is its own reward.</item>
    <item>Modulation in all things.</item>
    <item>A user and his leisure time are soon parted.</item>
    <item>There\'s no place like http://www.home.com</item>
    <item>Know what to expect before you connect.</item>
    <item>Oh, what a tangled website we weave when first we practice.</item>
    <item>Speed thrills.</item>
    <item>Give a man a fish and you feed him for a day; teach him to use the Net and he won\'t bother you for weeks.</item>
</string-array>
</resources>